A Guide to the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Executive Journals 1992
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Secretary of the Commonwealth, Executive Journals, 1992
Library of Virginia
34628
9 cubic feet
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Restorations of rights, pardons granted, extradition renditions and requisitions are restricted (public access and photoduplication) to those with written authorization from the Secretary of the Commonwealth. Guide to the collection available in Archives Manuscript Room.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth on April 1, 1994.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth has evolved from early colonial times when there existed a Secretary of the Colony. Thomas Nelson held the position of the first Secretary of Virginia in 1776. Early Secretaries were elected by the public. An Act of the General Assembly in 1920 changed the election to a joint vote of the General Assembly. In a 1930 Act the duties of the Secretary were redefined with the Secretary of the Commonwealth serving as the ex officio secretary of the Governor, as custodian of many official State records, and as keeper of the Greater and Lesser Seals of the Commonwealth. The office of the Secretary has gradually acquired other functions, such as: service of out-of-state civil process; appointment and regulation of notaries public; and registration and oversight of lobbyists. The Office became a gubernatorial appointment subsequent to a 1958 Act of the Assembly. The Secretary of the Commonwealth is under the jurisdiction of the Governor's Office.
The Secretary is appointed by the Governor for a term of four years. Currently the Secretary of the Commonwealth is responsible for gubernatorial appointments, clemency and restoration of civil rights requests and extraditions. Additional activities include: serving as ex officio Secretary to the Governor; serving as keeper of the seals of the Commonwealth; compiling and publishing the annual Blue Book; commissioning and regulating notary publics, including the publication of a Notary Handbook and conduct of disciplinary hearings; promulgating the lobbying disclosure requirements, registration of lobbyists, and recording of lobbying reports; servicing the civil process of out-of-state defendants and other parties; and authenticating and certifying the records of the courts and of any state agency. Governor-elect James Gilmore appointed Anne P. Petera, chairwoman of the State Alcoholic Beverage Control Board in the Allen Administration, secretary. Petera served until the end of Gilmore's administration in January 2002.
Scope and Content
The Executive Journals of the Secretary of the Commonwealth contain the permanent record of the Governor's appointments, executive orders and memorandums, commissions, notaries, pardons, writs of election, restoration of rights, renditions and requisitions. This accession consists of the records of the third year of Governor Lawrence D. Wilder's administration (January-December, 1992).
Arrangement
The records for Governor Wilder are arranged by date then type of record, alphabetically.
Contents List
- List of Contents, 1992 January-July (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Appointments, 1992 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Appointments, 1992 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Appointments, 1992 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Appointments, 1992 January 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Appointments, 1992 January 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Appointments, 1992 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Appointments, 1992 January 29 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Appointments, 1992 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 3 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 6 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 7 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 13 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 21 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 29 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 January 2 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 January 3 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 January 6 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 January 13 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 January 20 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 January 29 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Notaries, 1992 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Notaries, 1992 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Proclamations, 1992 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Appointments, 1992 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 10 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 19 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 24 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Notaries, 1992 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Notaries, 1992 February 21 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Appointments, 1992 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Appointments, 1992 March 18 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Appointments, 1992 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 10 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 17 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 20 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 March 18 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Notaries, 1992 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Notaries, 1992 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Orders, 1992 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Proclamations, 1992 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Writ of Election, 1992 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Appointments, 1992 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Appointments, 1992 April 28 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 100)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 April 13 (Box 1, Folder 102)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Notaries, 1992 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Notaries, 1992 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Orders, 1992 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- Proclamations, 1992 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- Appointments, 1992 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Appointments, 1992 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Appointments, 1992 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 112)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 May 8 (Box 1, Folder 114)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 116)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 117)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Notaries, 1992 May 8 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- Notaries, 1992 May 22 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- Orders, 1992 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Orders, 1992 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 126)
- Appointments, 1992 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 127)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 130)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 11 (Box 1, Folder 131)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 132)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 133)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 134)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 135)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 22 (Box 1, Folder 136)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 23 (Box 1, Folder 137)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 138)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 26 (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 140)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 141)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 142)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 143)
- Notaries, 1992 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 144)
- Notaries, 1992 June 17 (Box 1, Folder 145)
- Orders, 1992 June 2 (Box 1, Folder 146)
- Orders, 1992 June 11 (Box 1, Folder 147)
- Appointments, 1992 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 148)
- Appointments, 1992 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 149)
- Appointments, 1992 July 20 (Box 1, Folder 150)
- Appointments, 1992 July 22 (Box 1, Folder 151)
- Appointments, 1992 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 152)
- Appointments, 1992 July 30 (Box 1, Folder 153)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 154)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 6 (Box 1, Folder 155)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 7 (Box 1, Folder 156)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 157)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 14 (Box 1, Folder 158)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 15 (Box 1, Folder 159)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 16 (Box 1, Folder 160)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 161)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 20 (Box 1, Folder 162)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 22 (Box 1, Folder 163)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 22 (Box 1, Folder 164)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 165)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 166)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 167)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 29 (Box 1, Folder 168)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 30 (Box 1, Folder 169)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 170)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 171)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 July 14 (Box 1, Folder 172)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 July 30 (Box 1, Folder 173)
- Notaries, 1992 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 174)
- Notaries, 1992 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 175)
- Notaries, 1992 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 176)
- Orders, 1992 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 177)
- Orders, 1992 July 29 (Box 1, Folder 178)
- Proclamations, 1992 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 179)
- List of Contents, 1992 August-December (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Appointments, 1992 August 4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Appointments, 1992 August 6 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Appointments, 1992 August 14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Appointments, 1992 August 19 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Appointments, 1992 August 21 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 4 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 5 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 6 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 7 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 11 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 12 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 13 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 14 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 17 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 18 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 19 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 20 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 21 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 24 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 25 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 28 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 August 31 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 August 6 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 August 19 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 August 21 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 August 26 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Notaries, 1992 August 5 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Notaries, 1992 August 19 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Orders, 1992 August 6 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Orders, 1992 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Orders, 1992 August 28 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Proclamations, 1992 August 3 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Appointments, 1992 September 1 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Appointments, 1992 September 4 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Appointments, 1992 September 15 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Appointments, 1992 September 18 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Appointments, 1992 September 21 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Appointments, 1992 September 25 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Appointments, 1992 September 29 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 1 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 2 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 3 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 4 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 7 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 8 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 9 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 10 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 14 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 15 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 18 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 19 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 21 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 22 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 23 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 24 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 25 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 28 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 29 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 30 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 September 4 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 September 18 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 September 25 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 September 27 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 September 28 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Notaries, 1992 September 2 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Notaries, 1992 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Notaries, 1992 September 28 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Notaries, 1992 September 29 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Notaries, 1992 September 30 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Orders, 1992 September 3 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Orders, 1992 September 21 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Orders, 1992 September 28 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Appointments, 1992 November 5 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Appointments, 1992 November 12 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Appointments, 1992 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Appointments, 1992 November 19 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Appointments, 1992 November 25 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 2 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 3 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 4 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 5 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 6 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 9 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 12 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 13 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 16 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 17 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 20 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 24 (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 25 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 November 5 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 November 11 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 November 16 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 November 24 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 November 25 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Notaries, 1992 November 4 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Notaries, 1992 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Notaries, 1992 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Notaries, 1992 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Notaries, 1992 November 25 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Orders, 1992 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Proclamations, 1992 November 13 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Proclamations, 1992 November 27 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Writ of Election, 1992 November 9 (Box 2, Folder 119)
- Writ of Election, 1992 November 12 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Appointments, 1992 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 121)
- Appointments, 1992 December 11 (Box 2, Folder 122)
- Appointments, 1992 December 17 (Box 2, Folder 123)
- Appointments, 1992 December 22 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 1 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 2 (Box 2, Folder 126)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 3 (Box 2, Folder 127)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 128)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 129)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 131)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 132)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 11 (Box 2, Folder 133)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 14 (Box 2, Folder 134)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 16 (Box 2, Folder 136)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 21 (Box 2, Folder 137)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 22 (Box 2, Folder 138)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 23 (Box 2, Folder 139)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 29 (Box 2, Folder 140)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 30 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 December 2 (Box 2, Folder 142)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 143)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 144)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 145)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 December 22 (Box 2, Folder 146)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1992 December 29 (Box 2, Folder 147)
- Memorandum, 1992 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 148)
- Memorandum, 1992 December 16 (Box 2, Folder 149)
- Notaries, 1992 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 150)
- Notaries, 1992 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 151)
- Notaries, 1992 December 14 (Box 2, Folder 152)
- Notaries, 1992 December 21 (Box 2, Folder 153)
- Notaries, 1992 December 23 (Box 2, Folder 154)
- Notaries, 1992 December 30 (Box 2, Folder 155)
- Orders, 1992 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 156)
- Orders, 1992 December 11 (Box 2, Folder 157)
- Orders, 1992 December 18 (Box 2, Folder 158)
- Orders, 1992 December 19 (Box 2, Folder 159)
- Orders, 1992 December 21 (Box 2, Folder 160)
- Writ of Election, 1992 December 18 (Box 2, Folder 161)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 January 21 (Box 2, Folder 162)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 January 29 (Box 2, Folder 163)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 February 25 (Box 2, Folder 164)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 March 12 (Box 2, Folder 165)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 March 26 (Box 2, Folder 166)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 April 7 (Box 2, Folder 167)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 168)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 169)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 July 8 (Box 2, Folder 170)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 July 10 (Box 2, Folder 171)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 July 20 (Box 2, Folder 172)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 July 22 (Box 2, Folder 173)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 August 6 (Box 2, Folder 174)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 August 21 (Box 2, Folder 175)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 September 1 (Box 2, Folder 176)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 September 25 (Box 2, Folder 177)
- Addendum, Appointments, 1992 November 5 (Box 2, Folder 178)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 5 (Box 2, Folder 179)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 6 (Box 2, Folder 180)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 181)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 8 (Box 2, Folder 182)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 183)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 13 (Box 2, Folder 184)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 15 (Box 2, Folder 185)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 16 (Box 2, Folder 186)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 18 (Box 2, Folder 187)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 21 (Box 2, Folder 188)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 22 (Box 2, Folder 189)